Okay, so your AI assistant just wrote
40 test cases in nine seconds, and
they all look right, but there's
one that's was skipped, and that's
the one that will be shipped
So I'm Scotty Crump.
I'm a lead software developer
engineer in test, and I'm a
ISTQB certified instructor.
So this course that I've created is for
testers that's already using generative
AI also for ones who are about to and who
have the goal of wanting to use it well
so what you'll learn in the course is
how to turn a requirement into a prompt
that returns reusable test ideas and
apply that across test analysis, test
design, and automated regression testing
Then comes the harder half spotting
hallucinations and reasoning errors
handling non-deterministic results
and protecting your test data from
privacy and prompt injection risk
so we'll go past the chatbot and
we'll look at things like retrieval,
agents, fine-tuning, and LLM ops
and real test infrastructure.
And we'll also look at an
adoption strategy that your
organization will back you up on
so every lesson is gonna be paired with
a guided demo and hands-on worksheets
and knowledge checks so that you're not
just watching the videos, you'll also
be actually applying the skill, which
is gonna really drive the knowledge into
your long-term memory and ultimately
help you in either the exam or when
you're actually working on the job
so we have 37 lessons spread out
over five chapters, and it's gonna
cover the whole CT GenAI syllabus.
And so every lesson's gonna be
mapped to an exam objective.
And you don't need any prior GenAI
experience, although at this point
everyone has at least dabbled
in using AI assistants and stuff
so take a few moments and skim through
some of the free lessons that I provided,
and if you feel like this course would
be a good fit for your learning goals,
then enroll today and let's get started